Finding Aid for the Collection of Underground, Alternative and Extremist Literature LSC.0050
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Organization Materials
  - B
    - Better American Federation of California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 37)
    - Biafra Children's Relief Committee. Santa Monica, California. (Box 37)
    - Big business, n.p. (Box 37)
    - Black Fire. Emeryville, California. (Box 37)
    - Black Flag Anarchists. New York, New York. (Box 37)
    - Black Guard. East Los Angeles, California. (Box 37)
    - Black Panther Party, n.p. (Box 38)
      - People's news service, 1970 April 30 (Box 38)
      - Mass rally: free Huey!, 1968 (Box 38)
      - Support the Panthers, 1971 February (Box 38)
        Scope and Contents note
        Committee asks for financial support for the "LA 18" whose trial is coming up.
      - Free Geronimo, 1972 May (Box 38)
      - Stop the federal conspiracy!, undated (Box 38)
      - We need the people!, 1969 December (Box 38)
      - Alprentice "Bunchy" Carter People's Medical Center, 1970 (Box 38)
      - Free busing program, 1970 (Box 38)
      - Free the LA 13: on trial for their lives, 1971 August (Box 38)
    - Black Power, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Black Student Union, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Black Unitarians for Radical Reform. Los Angeles, California. (Box 38)
      - Bro. Mxolisi Ntlabati, 1968 March (Box 38)
        Handwritten flier announcing the appearance of Ntlabati at the Los Angeles Unitarian Church.
      - Another public service from Black Unitarians for Radical Reform, 1968 March (Box 38)
        Excerpts from two Los Angeles Times articles written by Meisler.
    - Bobby Seale Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 38)
    - Bookmailer. New York, New York. (Box 38)
    - Bookniga, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 38)
    - Boycott, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Brazil - Politics and goverment, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Bretton Woods, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Britain-China Friendship Association. London, England. (Box 38)
    - British Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners in Russia. London, England. (Box 38)
    - British Israel Association. Vancouver, B.C. (Box 38)
    - British Socialist Party, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Britons Publishing Society. London, England. (Box 38)
    - Broadcasts, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 38)
    - Brooks Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 38)
    - Brown Berets, n.p. (Box 38)
      - Brown Berets: to serve, observe and protect, undated (Box 38)
      - Viva La Raza: A.P.E. presents a benefit for the Brown Berets, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Brown, H. Rap, n.p. (Box 38)
    - Bund Club of New York, n.p. (Box 38)
  - C
    - California Democrats for Wallace. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Anti-Communist League. Lancaster, California. (Box 39)
    - California Anti-Racket Association, n.p. (Box 39)
    - California Anti-Vivisection Society. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Clipper (Editorial Service). Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Committee Against Conscription. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Committee for Economic Freedom. Los Gatos, California. (Box 39)
    - California Committee for Mental Health. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Committee for the Republic. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Democratic Council, n.p. (Box 39)
    - California Emergency Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California Free Enterprise Association, n.p. (Box 39)
    - California Humane Council. Woodland Hills, California. (Box 39)
    - California League of Conservation Voters. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - California League of Senior Citizens, n.p. (Box 39)
    - California Pension Plan. Hollywood, California. (Box 39)
    - California Socialist Party, n.p. (Box 39)
    - California State Industrial Union Council. San Francisco, California. (Box 39)
    - California Tax Reduction Movement. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - Californians Against State Executions. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - Californians Against Waste. Sacramento, California. (Box 39)
    - Californians for Brown, n.p. (Box 39)
    - Californians for Justice in Education. Los Angeles, California. (Box 39)
    - Californians for Liberal Representation, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Cambodian Crisis Coalition. Los Angeles, California. (Box 40)
    - Campaign Against Utility Service Exploitation. Los Angeles, California. (Box 40)
    - Campaign for Democratic Freedom. Marina Del Ray, California. (Box 40)
    - Campaign for Economic Democracy. Santa Monica, California. (Box 40)
    - Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament. London, England. (Box 40)
    - Campaign literature, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Campus Forum - An Independent Journal of News and Expression. El Camino College, California. (Box 40)
    - Canadian Free Enterprise Newsletter. Toronto, Canada. (Box 40)
    - Canadian Intelligence Publications, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Canadian Labor Defense League, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Canadian Soviet Friendship Society. Toronto, Canada. (Box 40)
    - Cancer Control Society. Los Angeles, California. (Box 40)
    - Candour Publishing Company, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Capitalist (published by Brigham Young University Young Conservative Club). Provo, Utah. (Box 40)
    - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Care. New York, New York. (Box 40)
    - Caribbean, n.p. (Box 40)
    - Carta Legislativa. Los Angeles, California. (Box 40)
    - Catalytic Circle. St. Louis, Missouri. (Box 40)
    - Catholic Agitator. Los Angeles, California. (Box 41)
    - Catholic Human Relations Council of Los Angeles, n.p. (Box 41)
    - Catholic Traditionalist Movement. New York, New York. (Box 41)
    - Catholic Worker, n.p. (Box 41)
    - Catholics for Delano Families, n.p. (Box 41)
    - Catolicos por La Raza. Los Angeles, California. (Box 41)
    - Center for American Studies. Glendale, California. (Box 41)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights. New York, New York. (Box 41)
    - Center for Environmental Education. Washington, D.C. (Box 42)
    - Center for Law in the Public Interest. Los Angeles, California. (Box 42)
    - Central Board for Conscientious Objectors. London, England. (Box 42)
    - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors, n.p. (Box 42)
    - Central Standing Committee of General Association of Korean Residents in Japan, Tokyo. (Box 42)
    - Central Sunbathing Association. Louisville, Kentucky. (Box 42)
    - Charles H. Kerr & Company, n.p. (Box 42)
    - Charter Protective League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 43)
    - Chest for Liberation of Workers of Europe, n.p. (Box 43)
    - Chicago Defense Committee. New York, New York. (Box 43)
    - Chicago Women's Committee to Free Joanne Little. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 43)
    - Chicano Moratorium Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 43)
    - Child labor, n.p. (Box 43)
    - Chile, n.p. (Box 43)
    - China, n.p. (Box 43)
    - China Aid Council. New York, New York. (Box 43)
    - China Information Bureau, n.p. (Box 43)
    - China Information Committee. Hankow, China. (Box 43)
    - Chinese Association for the United Nations, n.p. (Box 43)
    - Chinese Cultural Society. New York, New York. (Box 43)
    - Chinese Students' Association of Southern California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 43)
    - Christ of the Ozarks, n.p. (Box 43)
    - Christian American Crusade. Los Angeles, California. (Box 43)
    - Christian American Democracy Now, n.p. (Box 43)
    - Christian American Guards. Los Angeles, California. (Box 43)
    - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade. Long Beach, California. (Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47)
    - Christian Crusade. Tulsa, Oklahoma. (Box 48)
    - Christian Educational Association. Union, New Jersey. (Box 49)
    - Christian Front for Peace and Against Fascism. Hollywood, California. (Box 49)
    - Christian National Party. St Louis, Missouri. (Box 49)
    - Christian Nationalist Crusade. Los Angeles, California. (Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52)
    - Citizen Research Institute. Los Angeles, California. (Box 61)
    - Citizen's Committee for the Defense of Mexican-American Youth. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee for Resettlement ... Japanese Evacuees. St. Louis, Missouri. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee of California, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee to Aid Locked out Hearst Employees, n.p. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Committee to Save Elysian Park. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Conference on International Union. New York, New York. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Councils of America, n.p. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Emergency Defense Conference. New York, New York. (Box 60)
    - Citizens for Constructive Action, n.p. (Box 60)
    - Citizens for Decency through Law, Incorporated, Cleveland (Box 60)
    - Citizens for Decent Literature. Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 60)
    - Citizens for LaRouche. New York, New York. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee (To Aid American Taxpayers). Washington, D.C. (Box 60)
    - Citizens Intelligence Digest. Bakersfield, California. (Box 61)
    - Citizens Joint Commission of Inquiry on South Chicago Memorial Day Incident 1937. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 61)
    - Citizens' Charter Protective Committee, n.p. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes In Vietnam. New York, New York. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Committee for Nuclear Disarmament. San Francisco, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Committee for Old Age Pensions. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Committee to Free Earl Browder. New York, New York. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Federation to Vote NO on 25. Los Angeles, California. (Box 60)
    - Citizens' Organization for a Sane World, n.p. (Box 61)
    - Citizens' Power Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 61)
    - Civic Assocation of America. Hollywood, California. (Box 61)
    - Civic Center Record. Los Angeles, California. (Box 61)
    - Civic Research-Action Group. Los Angeles, California. (Box 61)
    - Civic Service Association. Hollywood, California. (Box 61)
    - Civil Rights, n.p. (Box 61, Box 62, Box 63)
    - Civil Rights - Indians, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Civil Rights - Korea, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Civil Rights - Union of South Africa, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Civil Rights Congress. Los Angeles, California. (Box 64)
    - Civil Rights Congress. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Civil Rights Defense Committee. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Clark County Welfare Rights Organization. Las Vegas, Nevada. (Box 64)
    - Clergy and Laity Concerned. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Clergy and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Co-operative Publishing Society of Foreign Workers in USSR, Moscow. (Box 87)
    - Co-operative Union Limited. Manchester, England. (Box 87)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy. Los Angeles, California. (Box 64)
    - Coalition for Economic Survival. Los Angeles, California. (Box 64)
    - Coalition for Full Employment. Pacoima, California. (Box 64)
    - Coalition for Handgun Control. Los Angeles, California. (Box 64)
    - Coalition on National Priorites and Military Policy. Washington, D.C. (Box 64)
    - Cockerel Print. Wellington, England. (Box 64)
    - Collectivism, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Collectivist Press. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. (Box 64)
    - Commission on International Relations of the National Conference on the Christian Way of Life. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Commission on Money and Credit. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy. New York, New York. (Box 64)
    - Committee for a Democratic Foreign Policy, n.p. (Box 64)
    - Committee for a Democratic Spain. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterlization Abuse (CARASA). Venice, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Amnesty for All Objectors to War and Conscription. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Choice in California. Venice, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Citizenship Rights. San Francisco, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Economic Development. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Ethiopian Jewry. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Freedom of the Press. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for International Workers Aid. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Jews of Poland. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Jobs and Lower Prices. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Justice in Education. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Leo Koch. New Hyde Park, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Nonviolent Action. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Responsible University Government, n.p. (Box 65)
    - Committee for the Defense of Civil Rights in Tampa. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee for the Freedom of the Press. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for the Preservation of the Democratic Party of California, n.p. (Box 65)
    - Committee for the Rights of the Disabled, Incorporated. Huntington Park, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee for the Workers' Rights Amendment. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 65)
    - Committee for Traditional Indian Land and Life. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee in Defense of Carl Marzini. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the Peoples of El Salvador. Los Angeles, California. (Box 65)
    - Committee of 100. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee of First Amendment Defendants. New York, New York. (Box 65)
    - Committee of One Million (Against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations), n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee of Religious Concern for Peace Now. Los Angeles, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee of Responsibility, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Committee of Southern Churchmen. Nashville, Tennessee. (Box 66)
    - Committee of Teachers to Elect Max Rafferty, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee of the States. Lincoln, Nebraska. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Coal and Giant Power. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Fair Play in Spirts. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Japanese Legislation Native Sons of the Golden West. San Francisco, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Jewish Americana, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Media Accountability. Santa Monica, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Militarism in Education. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Pan-American Policy, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Political Education. Washington, D.C. (Box 66)
    - Committee on Soviet Jewry of the Jewish Federation Council of Greater Los Angeles, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee on World Peace and Foreign Relations, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Aid American War Objectors. Vancouver, Canada. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Aid the Monroe Defendants. Los Angeles, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Defend Resistance to Ghetto Life. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Free Morton Sobell, n.p. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Free the Hollywood Ten. Hollywood, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Organize the Advancement of Women. Los Angeles, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Reinstate Mort Sahl. Los Angeles, California. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Restore the Constitution. Fort Collins, Colorado. (Box 66)
    - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell. New York, New York. (Box 66)
    - Common Cause. Washington, D.C. (Box 67)
    - Common Council for American Unity. New York, New York. (Box 68)
    - Commonwealth Tax Plan, SAFER-USA. Los Angeles, California. (Box 68)
    - Communism
      - n.p. (Box 68)
      - Argentina, n.p. (Box 69)
      - Asia, Southeastern, n.p. (Box 69)
      - Australia, n.p. (Box 69)
      - Brazil, n.p. (Box 69)
      - Bulgaria, n.p. (Box 69)
      - Canada, n.p. (Box 69)
      - China, n.p. (Box 70)
      - Colombia, n.p. (Box 76)
      - Costa Rica, n.p. (Box 76)
      - Czechoslovakia, n.p. (Box 76)
      - Dominican Republic, n.p. (Box 76)
      - Europe, n.p. (Box 76)
      - Finland, n.p. (Box 76)
      - France, n.p. (Box 77)
      - Germany, Eastern, n.p. (Box 77)
      - Great Britain, n.p. (Box 77)
      - Hungary, n.p. (Box 78)
      - India, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Ireland, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Italy, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Korea, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Mexico, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Poland, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Rumania, n.p. (Box 78)
      - Russia, n.p. (Box 72-74, 79-81)
      - Spain, n.p. (Box 74)
      - Tibet, n.p. (Box 74)
      - U.S., n.p. (Box 74, Box 75)
      - Venezuela, n.p. (Box 75)
      - Vietnam, n.p. (Box 75)
      - Yugoslavia, n.p. (Box 75)
      - Cuba, n.p. (Box 76)
    - Communist International. New York, New York. (Box 82)
    - Communist Labor Party of America, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Communist League of America, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Communist League of America (Opposition), n.p. (Box 82)
    - Communist Party of California, n.p. (Box 82)
    - Communist Party of Great Britain, n.p. (Box 82, Box 83)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America, n.p. (Box 84, Box 85)
    - Communist Youth Opposition. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Community for Social Education and Awareness. Los Angeles, California. (Box 85)
    - Community Leaders of Los Angeles City and County. Los Angeles, California. (Box 85)
    - Community Organization for Full Employment Economy, Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 85)
    - Community Relations Conference of Southern California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 85)
    - Community Relations Service. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Comrade Co-operative Company. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Concern for Dying. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Concerned Arcadians. Arcadia, California. (Box 85)
    - Concerned Bicycle Riders for the Environment. Los Angeles, California. (Box 85)
    - Concerned Homeowners of Santa Monica. Santa Monica, California. (Box 85)
    - Concord Press. Mount Vernon, Washington. (Box 85)
    - Confernece for Progressive Labor Action. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Conference to Strengthen American-Soviet Relations, n.p. (Box 85)
    - Congress of American-Soviet Friendship. New York, New York. (Box 85)
    - Congress of Racial Equality, n.p. (Box 85)
    - Conservative & liberal publications, n.p. (Box 86)
    - Conservative Book Club, New Rochell. New York, New York. (Box 86)
    - Conservative Society of America. New Orleans, Louisiana. (Box 86)
    - Constitution Party, n.p. (Box 86)
    - Constitutional Educational League, Incorporated. New Haven, Connecticut. (Box 86)
    - Constitutional Liberties Information Center. Los Angeles, California. (Box 86)
    - Constitutional Liberty League of Southern California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 86)
    - Constitutional Money League of America. Minden, Nebraska. (Box 86)
    - Constitutional Rights Foundation. Los Angeles, California. (Box 86)
    - Construction Action, Incorporated. Whittier, California. (Box 86)
    - Consumers' Shield. Los Angeles, California. (Box 86)
    - Contemporary Publishing Association. New York, New York. (Box 86)
    - Continental Congress of Farmers and Workers. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 86)
    - Continuation Committee of National Conference on the Native Bills. Cape, Tennessee. (Box 86)
    - Controversy. San Francisco, California. (Box 86)
    - Cooperative Committee. Oakland, California. (Box 86)
    - Cooperative League. New York, New York. (Box 86)
    - Cooperative League of the USA. New York, New York. (Box 86)
    - Cooperative societies, n.p. (Box 87)
    - Council for a Livable World. Washington, D.C. (Box 87)
    - Council for Correspondence Newsletter. Cambridge, Massachusetts. (Box 87)
    - Council for Democracy, n.p. (Box 87)
    - Council for Individual Freedom. Portland, Indiana. (Box 82)
    - Council for Pan American Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 88)
    - Council for Planning and Conservation. Beverly Hills, California. (Box 82)
    - Council for Social Action of the Congregational and Christian Churches of America. New York, New York. (Box 88)
    - Council of the Women's International Democratic Federation, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Council on African Affairs. New York, New York. (Box 88)
    - Council on Economic Priorities. Washington, D.C. (Box 88)
    - Council on World Tensions, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Crisis. Los Angeles, California. (Box 88)
    - Critics Group. New York, New York. (Box 88)
    - Crusader of Florida. Jacksonville, Florida. (Box 88)
    - Crusaders for Economic Liberty, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Cuba - Politics and government, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Cuban Missile Crisis,, n.p., October 1962 (Box 88)
  - D
    - Daily People's World. San Francisco, California. (Box 88)
    - Daily Worker Publishing Company, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Dan Smoot Report. Dallas, Texas. (Box 88)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution. National Defense Committee, n.p. (Box 88)
    - Declaration Press. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. (Box 89)
    - Defender Magazine. Wichita, Kansas (Box 89)
    - Defenders of 3 Against HUAC. Washington, D.C. (Box 89)
    - Defenders of Animal Rights. Baltimore, Maryland. (Box 89)
    - Defenders of the American Constitution. Orlando Beach, Florida. (Box 89)
    - Defenders, Incorporated. Kansas City, Missouri. (Box 89)
    - Defense Committee for the Pittsburgh Six. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. (Box 89)
    - Defense of Literature and the Arts Fund. London, England. (Box 89)
    - Democrats for a Peaceful Solution. Los Angeles, California. (Box 89)
    - Demonstrators, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Denominational Affairs Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 89)
    - Deserters' Amnesty Campaign. London, England. (Box 89)
    - Disabled War Veterans and Widows Protective League, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Disarmament, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Discussions Unlimited. Los Angeles, California. (Box 89)
    - Dissenting Democrats. Beverly Hills, California. (Box 89)
    - Dominion Republic - Politics and government, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Don Bell Reports. Palm Beach, Florida. (Box 89)
    - Dow Action Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 89)
    - Drugs, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Dumbarton Oaks, n.p. (Box 89)
  - E
    - East Pasadena Firearms. Pasadena, California. (Box 89)
    - Echo Park - Silverlake Committee on the Crisis in American Foreign Policy. Los Angeles, California. (Box 89)
    - Ecology, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Economic Research Corporation. Barrington, Illinois. (Box 89)
    - Economic League. New York, New York. (Box 89)
    - Economic Theory, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Economics, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Economists' National Committee on Monetary Policy. New York, New York. (Box 89)
    - Edmondson Economic Service. New York, New York. (Box 89)
    - Education, n.p. (Box 89)
    - Education - Controversial literature, n.p. (Box 90)
    - Education Department of Hadassah. New York, New York. (Box 90)
    - Effective Thinking Foundation. Hollywood, California. (Box 90)
    - Embassy of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics. Washington, D.C. (Box 90)
    - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee. New York, New York. (Box 90)
      SEE ALSO: Rights, New York.
    - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, n.p. (Box 90)
    - Emergency Committee for Chinese Refugees, n.p. (Box 90)
    - Emergency Committee for Vietnamese Relief, Berkeley. (Box 90)